<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Donald Schulz Project</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Donald Schulz Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 19:19:42 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>April to July 2023, Schedule of Releases</title>
      <link>/post/april_to_july_2023_schedule_of_releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 19:19:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/april_to_july_2023_schedule_of_releases/</guid>
      <description>Instead of coming out with an album is about 4 months I am going to be doing regular releases roughly about every two weeks. I am still planning to package a number of these songs into the album that I had planned but this way you get to ride along with me as I get the pieces put together. As a result I even have a rough schedule of the dates and which song will be released at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Always On My Mind</title>
      <link>/songs/always-on-my-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/always-on-my-mind/</guid>
      <description>This is a sad song and yes it really happened to me. I think this was probably the first time that I really fell in love and one of those situations where I new there was an expiry date and yet the heart wants what the heart wants. This break up really did a number on me as I lost my confidence and became very cold and almost distant to other relationships that I had after this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Date Announced</title>
      <link>/post/release_date_announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:19:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/release_date_announced/</guid>
      <description>We will be releasing our first single &amp;ldquo;Hot Java&amp;rdquo; on February 24, 2023. It should be available on all your favorite streaming services, where ever you get your music from. I am hoping for some good numbers here and hope that you will help us to get the word out. Hot Java is an instrumental and even though I have put this in the jazz and blues genre, it has a lot of elements of pop and rock, very fusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Java</title>
      <link>/songs/hot-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/hot-java/</guid>
      <description>This music was performed for the first time at my Mom and Dad&amp;rsquo;s 25th Wedding Anniversary. Several years later I rearranged the music and recording this in a 24 track studio in Edmonton, Alberta with some friends and some additional professional musicians. This became a very limited release and one of the last things that I pressed into a vinyl record. The music centers around a good cup of coffee. One of the signs that indicated to us as kids that company was coming was sound of the very loud percolator that would be whooshing away making that hot cup of java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About The Donald Schulz Project</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Donald Schulz Project&amp;rdquo; A little bit about who I am, my name is Donald Schulz and I was born grew up just outside of Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. I was quite active in the music scene during the 70&amp;rsquo;s and 80&amp;rsquo;s. It was a different time and I loved working on music and the community. Music was my initial passion. I have been writing songs since I was about 12 and I forced my bother to sing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Playlists on Spotify</title>
      <link>/playlists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
